# **PAULOS NIGUSSIE GEBETA**

# **Junior Frontend Web Developer**

**\** +251 944-141-594

Addis Ababa, Ethiopia

@ pablonigussie1@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/paul-gebeta

# **SUMMARY**

Web developer with 4 years of experience in designing and creating visually appealing and interactive user interface. Knowledgeable in responsive design principles and modern front-end frameworks Seeking opportunity to expand reach and grow my experince and Network.

## **EXPERIENCE**

2022 - Present

Front End Developer

Addis Ababa, Ethiopia

- **Rendo creatives**
- · launched more than 10 websites
- · I spearheaded website optimization initiatives
- · implemented cutting-edge technologies
- streamlined development processes for improved efficiency.

2018 - 2022

Web Designer/Digital Marketer

**Zuret Addis Mag** Addis Ababa, Ethiopia

- · I gained hands-on experience in creating visual assets,
- Developed and designd main website of the company,
- Ran consecutive maketing campagns whic got a lot of traction
- Maintained and updated web page throug my time at the company

## **SKILLS**

**Problem Resolution** 

Seo optimization

Communications

Time management,

**Graphic Design** 

### **EDUCATION**

2013 - 2017

Marketing Managment **Unity University** 

### **STRENGTHS**

#### **Reliable and Trustworthy**

Take full responsibility to deliver my work in time and always hold myself accountable for goals and deadlines, consistently follow through on projects

#### **Great comunicator**

As a great listener, I prioritize active engagement and understanding in conversations. I value creating a comfortable environment where others feel heard and validated.

#### Life-long Learner

Never done learning and always seeking to improve myself, maintain growth mindset and eager to grow in my roles and responsibilities

> Powered by CV Enhancy

## **CERTIFICATION**

## Fullstack Web Developement

**ii** 2022 - 06/2023 **♀** Addis Ababa, Ethiopia

Udemy course

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, responsive design, frameworks.Back-end Development: Server-side programming, databases, RESTful APIs, authentication.
- Deployment and Hosting: Server/cloud deployment, domain configuration.
- · Agile Development and Project Management: Project planning, task management



Powered by CY Enhancy